Jae Mahn Surh

Github: github.com/jaes16

Summary

- A computer science major at Williams
 College, with experience of working on large projects.
- Adaptable to different working environments, and quick to learn different skill sets.
- Passionate about technology and experiencing how it affects the world firsthand.

Projects

Operating System Development (x86) github.com/jaes16/OS dev

- A personal passion project to learn OS development and get practice in managing large projects.
- Supports a basic memory manager, terminal use, and a file system roughly based on the FAT file system structure.

Log Structured File System Development github.com/jaes16/FS

- Another personal passion project to learn FS development and resource management.
- Provides most of the basic implementations needed for a file system and has rudimentary garbage collection.

Awards

Excellence in Service / 2021 National Health Insurance Service, Korea

Given by the president of the National Health Insurance Service to a social service agent that has worked exceptionally in aid of the NHIS.

Outstanding Performance in Training / 2019 Republic of Korea, Army

Given by the regimental commander to the top two trainees with the highest performance in bootcamp training. Email: js16@williams.edu

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/jae-mahn-surh-703

Phone: 010-6761-8239

Experience

Social Service Agent / 2019-2021 National Health Insurance Service, Korea

Assisted in customer service, the practice of safety measures for Covid-19, and overall maintenance of the North Seocho Division.

Computer Science Research Assistant / 2019 Williams College

Used the MATLAB implementation of general regression neural networks to predict the electric use in an all-electric building with an R² value of 0.9053.

Student Technology Consultant / 2017-2019 Williams College

Provided support for students and professors in utilizing the school's computers, servers, and various hardware, while helping the IT with maintenance of systems.

Education

GRE: 335/340

Williams College / 2016 – Major: Computer Science

GPA: 3.5

Operating Systems: A

Algorithm Design and Analysis: A

Storage Systems: A-

King's Academy, Jordan/2012 - 2016

The Masri Award Highest Honors

Skills

- Proficiency in C and Python
- Experience with the Flask framework, web development, web scraping, Java, C++, HTML, Microsoft Office
- Fluency in English and Korean